What's the minimum dose for building
muscle? As I don't seem very anabolic at
100 milligrams.
It's building muscle has nothing to do
with a dose. Building muscle has to do
with proper training, proper nutrition,
and proper sleep. Um, I don't see it
behind them now. I think that's a that's
a different book perhaps, that blue one.
But Steve wrote a book on diet and
training. I don't know if you have it
translated into English.
No, I have not. But uh Okay. All right.
There you
go. So, uh I would imagine he knows a
thing or two about lifting and eating
because he's just a physical specimen
over there. So, uh yeah, I mean, get get
if you know if if you speak Dutch, then
get uh get Steve's book. And if you
don't, maybe ask him for a referral to
an English version. Uh but learn how to
learn how to really train correctly for
your intended goal. Learn how to really
eat correctly for your intended goal and
make sure you get plenty of sleep
because nothing happens without good
sleep. I promise you it's not your
testosterone. It's really not. It's like
going on a journey in your car and then
saying, "What music should I play to get
there faster?" It's just like that's
just something in the journey. It really
is like the last bit of anything that
has to do with how quickly and how
effectively you're going to get to your
muscle goals. I've seen guys with low
tea build physiques and I've seen guys
with really good tea levels that lay on
the couch and do nothing actually look
like slops. So, I know you're probably
training, you think you're doing things
right. I'm not trying to be antagonistic
here, but here's the deal. If you're not
happy with your results, then your body
says otherwise. It's not about my
opinion, your opinion. The bottom line
is if your results are not happening,
then your input doesn't justify the
output. Change the input. Change it. All
right. Put the ego aside. Ask for help.
Research. Do your homework. You got to
lift with intent. Watch Sam Sulk. Watch
how that guy
trains. Guy trains to failure on every
damn set. Every set, he'll go to full
failure. Um, and that's what's required
to really cause muscle adaptation. Your
body's very content where it is. That's
why it's how it is. Whatever your body
you have right now is conducive to your
daily activities. your body adapted your
to your lifestyle. And if your body is
going to change, your lifestyle has to
change, your training has to change,
your nutrition has to change, your sleep
has to change. If you're doing
everything the same for the last year
and you got no results, change it. It's
not your 100 milligrams. I promise you,
it's not. I wish it was that easy. It's
not.
[Music]
Hey.